Guide to the National Education Association-Commissions records, 1918-1982 NEA1002.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Commission on Professional Rights and Responsibilities, 1922-1981; Series 2; 82.75 Linear Feet
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Public School Teachers Association, 1966; Series 2 (Box 919, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-PSTA [file 1/3], 1965-1967; Series 2 (Box 917, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-PSTA [file 2/3], 1965-1967; Series 2 (Box 917, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-PSTA [file 3/3], 1965-1967; Series 2 (Box 918, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Reports [file 1/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 919, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Reports [file 2/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 919, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Sanctions [file 1/2], 1967-1971; Series 2 (Box 920, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Sanctions [file 2/2], 1967-1971; Series 2 (Box 920, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Special Committee [file 1/2], 1964-1968; Series 2 (Box 920, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Special Committee [file 2/2], 1964-1968; Series 2 (Box 920, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Cecil County [file 1/2], 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 920, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Cecil County [file 2/2], 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 920, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Cecil County-Classroom Teachers Association [file 1/2], 1972; Series 2 (Box 921, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Cecil County-Classroom Teachers Association [file 2/2], 1972; Series 2 (Box 921, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Chaptico, 1964; Series 2 (Box 921, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Charles County, 1968; Series 2 (Box 921, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Carroll County #289, 1968; Series 2 (Box 921, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Greenbelt, 1965; Series 2 (Box 921, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Hyattsville, 1967; Series 2 (Box 921, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Montgomery County, 1965; Series 2 (Box 921, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Salisbury [file 1/2], 1963-1969; Series 2 (Box 922, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Salisbury [file 2/2], 1963-1969; Series 2 (Box 922, Folder 2)
    Contains 4 photos.
  - Investigations-Maryland-Worchester County, 1972; Series 2 (Box 922, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Massachusetts-New Bedford #226, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 922, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Massachusetts-North Middlesex [file 1/2], 1962-1963; Series 2 (Box 922, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Massachusetts-North Middlesex [file 2/2], 1962-1963; Series 2 (Box 922, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Massachusetts-Springfield #116, 1964-1968; Series 2 (Box 923, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Massachusetts-Williamstown #198, 1964-1966; Series 2 (Box 923, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Belleville, 1968; Series 2 (Box 923, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Davidson, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 923, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit #193 [file 1/2], 1965-1968; Series 2 (Box 923, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit #193 [file 2/2], 1965-1968; Series 2 (Box 923, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit #204, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 923, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Committee and Commission Approvals, 1967; Series 2 (Box 923, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-DEA Materials, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 924, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Documents, 1966; Series 2 (Box 924, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-First Draft, 1967; Series 2 (Box 924, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit #193-General, 1966; Series 2 (Box 924, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Inequality, Defacto Segregation and Attempts Tax Remedy [file 1/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 924, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Inequality, Defacto Segregation and Attempts Tax Remedy [file 2/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 924, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Material from County and State Agencies, 1965-1967; Series 2 (Box 925, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-MEA Materials, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 925, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-News Releases, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 925, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Newspaper Clippings [file 1/2], 1966; Series 2 (Box 925, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Newspaper Clippings [file 2/2], 1966; Series 2 (Box 925, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Northern Boycott, 1966; Series 2 (Box 925, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Notes and Memoranda, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 925, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Press Releases, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 926, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Racial Counts, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 926, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Report Clearances, 1967; Series 2 (Box 926, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Revisit, 1966; Series 2 (Box 926, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-School Finance Information, 1964-1966; Series 2 (Box 926, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Schools and School Visitations, 1966; Series 2 (Box 926, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Socio-Economic Data, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 926, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Special Committee [file 1/2], 1966-1968; Series 2 (Box 927, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Special Committee [file 2/2], 1966-1968; Series 2 (Box 927, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Suit, 1964-1966; Series 2 (Box 927, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Detroit-Tax Structure, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 927, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Flint, 1971; Series 2 (Box 927, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Grand Haven, 1973; Series 2 (Box 927, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Grand Rapids #128, 1955-1966; Series 2 (Box 928, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Lincoln Park #163, 1965; Series 2 (Box 928, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Menominee #226 [file 1/2], 1967; Series 2 (Box 928, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Menominee #226 [file 2/2], 1967; Series 2 (Box 928, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Menominee-Newspaper Clippings, 1967; Series 2 (Box 928, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Monroe, 1958; Series 2 (Box 928, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Utica #109 [file 1/2], 1965; Series 2 (Box 928, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Utica #109 [file 2/2], 1965; Series 2 (Box 928, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Michigan-Warren #211, 1966; Series 2 (Box 928, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Minnesota-Minneapolis #232 [file 1/2], 1957-1958; Series 2 (Box 929, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Minnesota-Minneapolis #232 [file 2/2], 1957-1958; Series 2 (Box 929, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Minnesota-Minneapolis-Newspaper Clippings, 1967; Series 2 (Box 929, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Minnesota-Minneapolis-Social Commitee, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 929, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Minnesota-Statewide-Background, 1967; Series 2 (Box 929, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Minnesota-University of Minnesota, 1964; Series 2 (Box 929, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Columbus #209, 1966-1968; Series 2 (Box 929, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Columbus-Clippings, 1966; Series 2 (Box 930, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Columbus-Special Committee, 1966; Series 2 (Box 930, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Desegregation-Displacement, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 930, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Desegregation-General, 1970; Series 2 (Box 930, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Desegregation-News Clippings, 1970; Series 2 (Box 930, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Desegregation-Southern Regional Council, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 930, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Desegregation-Technical Information Releases, 1970; Series 2 (Box 930, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Displacement of Negro Principals, 1968-1971; Series 2 (Box 930, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Mississippi and Louisiana Task Force III [file 1/2], 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 931, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Rosedale, 1969-1971; Series 2 (Box 931, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Mississippi-Shelby, 1968; Series 2 (Box 931, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Blue Springs #285, 1966; Series 2 (Box 931, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Carthage #286, 1968; Series 2 (Box 931, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Center City, 1969; Series 2 (Box 931, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Cuba [file 1/2], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 931, Folder 8)
    Included "Missouri School Laws", by Hubert Wheeler, 1966.
  - Investigations-Missouri-Cuba [file 2/2], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 932, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Hickman Mills, 1960; Series 2 (Box 932, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Hickman Mills-Aftermath, 1959-1964; Series 2 (Box 932, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Kansas City #122, 1964; Series 2 (Box 932, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Kansas City #235 [file 1/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 932, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Kansas City #235 [file 2/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 932, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Kansas City, 1969; Series 2 (Box 932, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Kirkwood #206, 1966; Series 2 (Box 932, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Louisiana #154, 1965; Series 2 (Box 932, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Mehlville #281 [file 1/3], 1967-1970; Series 2 (Box 933, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Mehlville #281 [file 2/3], 1967-1970; Series 2 (Box 933, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Mehlville #281 [file 3/3], 1967-1970; Series 2 (Box 933, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Mehlville-Fact-Finding, 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 933, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Missouri-North Kansas City #245, 1967; Series 2 (Box 933, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Springfield, 1945-1966; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Springfield-Aftermath, 1963-1964; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Springfield-Clippings, 1963; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Springfield-Comments about Report, 1963; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Springfield-Distribution, 1963; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Springfield-Documents, 1964; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Springfield-Material from Board Members, 1963; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Springfield-Questionnaire, 1963; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Springfield-Requests for Investigation, 1962-1963; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Springfield-Study Committee, 1962-1963; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-Missouri-Statewide, 1969; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-Missouri-University City #162, 1964-1968; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-Missouri-University City #273, 1967; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 13)
  - Investigations-Montana-Missoula-Aftermath, 1962; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 14)
  - Investigations-Nebraska-McCook, 1947-1952; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 15)
  - Investigations-Nebraska-Statewide #309, 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 934, Folder 16)
  - Investigations-Nebraska-Statewide-Documents [file 1/2], 1969; Series 2 (Box 935, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Nebraska-Statewide-Documents [file 2/2], 1969; Series 2 (Box 935, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Nebraska-Statewide-Miller Letter File, 1968-1969; Series 2 (Box 935, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Nebraska-Winnebago, 1968; Series 2 (Box 935, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Nevada-Clark County #314, 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 935, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Nevada-Statewide [file 1/2], 1969-1971; Series 2 (Box 935, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Nevada-Statewide [file 2/2], 1969-1971; Series 2 (Box 935, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Littleton, 1969; Series 2 (Box 936, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Manchester, 1965; Series 2 (Box 1519, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Manchester #103, 1964-1968; Series 2 (Box 936, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Manchester-Clippings, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 936, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Manchester-Documents, 1962-1965; Series 2 (Box 936, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Manchester-Draft, February 1965-March 1965; Series 2 (Box 936, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Manchester-Manchester Teachers Guild, 1964; Series 2 (Box 936, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Manchester-New Hampshire Education Association, 1964; Series 2 (Box 936, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Manchester-Press Releases, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 936, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Manchester-Special Committee, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 936, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Manchester-Strike, 1957-1958; Series 2 (Box 936, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Manchester-Summary of Situation and Notes, 1964; Series 2 (Box 937, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Monadnock, 1972; Series 2 (Box 937, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Newport-Aftermath, 1950; Series 2 (Box 937, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Somersworth, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 937, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide #265, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 937, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide, 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 937, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide-Adult Education, 1966; Series 2 (Box 937, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide-Clippings, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 937, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide-Fiscal-Local Tax Support Assessment, 1967; Series 2 (Box 937, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide-Preliminary Inquiry into Educational Conditions in New Hampshire, 1962-1967; Series 2 (Box 938, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide-Press, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 938, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide-Special Committee, 1968; Series 2 (Box 938, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide-Special Committee Listing and Correspondence, 1968; Series 2 (Box 938, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide-Student Achievement, 1964-1966; Series 2 (Box 938, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide-Students Enrollments, 1967; Series 2 (Box 938, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide-Supportive Personnel, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 938, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Hampshire-Statewide-Teachers, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 938, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Belleville [file 1/4], 1965-1970; Series 2 (Box 939, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Belleville [file 2/4], 1965-1970; Series 2 (Box 939, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Belleville [file 3/4], 1965-1970; Series 2 (Box 939, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Belleville [file 4/4], 1965-1970; Series 2 (Box 939, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Belleville-Durke v. NEA, 1967; Series 2 (Box 1002, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Belleville-Newspapers, February 1966; Series 2 (Box 939, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Belleville-Petitions [file 1/2], 1965; Series 2 (Box 940, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Belleville-Petitions [file 2/2], 1965; Series 2 (Box 940, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Hawthorne, 1958; Series 2 (Box 940, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Linden, 1964; Series 2 (Box 940, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-New Brunswick [file 1/2], 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 940, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-New Brunswick [file 2/2], 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 940, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Newark #210, 1966; Series 2 (Box 940, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Passail #329, 1971; Series 2 (Box 941, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Red Bank #310, 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 941, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Roselle #106, 1963-1964; Series 2 (Box 941, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Statewide-Higher Education, 1968; Series 2 (Box 941, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Trenton State College [file 1/2], 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 941, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Trenton State College [file 2/2], 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 941, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Warren Township, 1964; Series 2 (Box 941, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Woodstown, 1964; Series 2 (Box 941, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New Jersey-Wrightstown #147, 1962-1965; Series 2 (Box 941, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Fort Wingate, 1964-1970; Series 2 (Box 942, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Rio Arriba, 1964; Series 2 (Box 1519, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Rio Arriba, 1964; Series 2 (Box 942, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Rio Arriba-Aftermath, 1965; Series 2 (Box 942, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Rio Arriba-Documents, 1962-1964; Series 2 (Box 942, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Rio Arriba-Notes and Reference Material, 1964; Series 2 (Box 942, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Rio Arriba-Press Clippings, 1964; Series 2 (Box 942, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Rio Arriba-Press Releases, 1964; Series 2 (Box 942, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Rio Arriba-Report, 1964; Series 2 (Box 942, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Rio Arriba-Report Approvals from Special Committee and Commission, 1964; Series 2 (Box 942, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Rio Arriba-Report Drafts, 1964; Series 2 (Box 942, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Rio Arriba-Special Committee, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 943, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Administration Memos, 1959-1960; Series 2 (Box 943, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Aftermath, 1961-1964; Series 2 (Box 1041, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Arrangements for the Investigation, 1959-1960; Series 2 (Box 943, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Comments about Report, 1961; Series 2 (Box 1041, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Committee Evaluation, 1960; Series 2 (Box 1041, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Contract Forms and Board Policies, 1959-1960; Series 2 (Box 943, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Della Herrera, 1960; Series 2 (Box 943, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Distribution of Report, 1961; Series 2 (Box 943, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Documents, 1959-1960; Series 2 (Box 943, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Galley, 1960; Series 2 (Box 943, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-General, 1960-1962; Series 2 (Box 943, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Helen Zuelzke, 1959-1960; Series 2 (Box 943, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Information, 1959-1960; Series 2 (Box 944, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Legal Documents, 1959-1960; Series 2 (Box 944, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Lila Rawls, 1960; Series 2 (Box 944, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Mildred Roberson, 1960; Series 2 (Box 944, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Miscellaneous Issues, 1959-1960; Series 2 (Box 944, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Newspaper Clippings [file 1/2], 1959-1962; Series 2 (Box 944, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Newspaper Clippings [file 2/2], 1959-1962; Series 2 (Box 944, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Notes, 1960; Series 2 (Box 1041, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Preliminary Investigation, 1959; Series 2 (Box 945, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Press Releases, 1961; Series 2 (Box 945, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Request for an Investigation, 1959-1961; Series 2 (Box 945, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Special Committee, 1960-1962; Series 2 (Box 945, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Santa Fe-Teacher and Citizen Complaint, 1960; Series 2 (Box 945, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Statewide #254, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 1041, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Statewide-Material from NEA [file 1/2], 1967; Series 2 (Box 1041, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Statewide-Material from NEA [file 2/2], 1967; Series 2 (Box 1041, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Statewide-Meeting Transcripts and Committee Schedule, 1967; Series 2 (Box 945, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Statewide-NEA Research Materials, 1967; Series 2 (Box 945, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Statewide-Newspaper Clippings, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 1041, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Statewide-Notes and Drafts of Introduction and Background, 1961; Series 2 (Box 945, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New Mexico-Statewide-Special Committee, 1967; Series 2 (Box 1041, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-New York-Bethpage-Report of an Investigation, 1958-1964; Series 2 (Box 946, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo #107, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 946, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo #332, 1970-1972; Series 2 (Box 946, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo-Clippings, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 946, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo-Documents, 1964-1967; Series 2 (Box 946, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo-Draft (4-6-1965), April 1965; Series 2 (Box 946, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo-News Releases, 1965; Series 2 (Box 946, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo-Pre-Final Report, July 1965; Series 2 (Box 946, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo-Preliminary Statement, 1965; Series 2 (Box 946, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo-Press Releases, 1965; Series 2 (Box 947, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo-Report, 1965; Series 2 (Box 947, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo-Special Committee, 1965; Series 2 (Box 947, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New York-Buffalo-Third Draft (4-23-1965), Series 2 (Box 947, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New York-Central Square, 1964; Series 2 (Box 947, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New York-Hempstead #157, 1965; Series 2 (Box 947, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New York-Jamestown #221, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 947, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown #188, 1965; Series 2 (Box 947, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown, 1960-1962; Series 2 (Box 947, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-Aftermath, 1962-1965; Series 2 (Box 947, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-Better Education League, 1960; Series 2 (Box 948, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-Board of Education, 1960; Series 2 (Box 948, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-Campaign Literature, 1958-1959; Series 2 (Box 948, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-Comments about Report, 1962; Series 2 (Box 948, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-District #5 Council of PTAs, 1960; Series 2 (Box 948, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-District #5 Education Association, 1952-1958; Series 2 (Box 948, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-Documents, 1951-1962; Series 2 (Box 948, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-Election Campaigns, 1958-1960; Series 2 (Box 948, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-HEB's Notes, 1960; Series 2 (Box 949, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-Information and Education Committee, 1957-1960; Series 2 (Box 949, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-New York-Levittown-Information and Education Committee, 1958; Series 2 (Box 949, Folder 3)